OK, so now we have our pad with paper, with some different fish species that we were interested in and some different points on them from the local fish dealer.
We're going to take that home and we're going to go online.
We're going to hop onto the internet and we're going to do our own search on each of those individual species of fish.
Not say that your fish dealer is lying to you or wrong, but different people have different opinions about things and sometimes have different personal experiences from different fish.
We want to make sure that we get a wide scope of information about these various different species.
I can?t stress enough that the key to keeping fish happy and healthy is research.
Find out as much about that fish as you possibly can.
You want to know where they come from.
You want to know how big they get.
You want to know what they eat.
You want to know how hardy they are.
You want to know their water requirements, be it PH and temperatures and things like that.
These are all important, especially if you?re putting together a community fish tank.
We?re going to need to find out all these different things about all these different fish that you want to try keeping.
And then, make sure that they're all within the same requirements.
We can't very well keep fish that have different temperature requirements or different PH requirements together because we will be compromising the health of one species or another.